{
    "id": "58eaad1953c94b63bf6995d03f4b2186",
    "title": "For, since, in and from: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f80d7f9ce2a64a20adc3565024b84ce2",
            "title": "For, Since, In And From",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I once studied the piano …………………… three years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That house has been empty ………………….. two years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known her ………………… a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We go away …………………. three weeks every summer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long are you here ……………………?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the worst storm …………………. years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be here ………………….. four o’clock onwards.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I work …………………. nine to five.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known her ………………….. three days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… the dawn of civilization, people have made war.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "since",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}